Sara Torkamani

Sales & Retail Assistant

Friendly and reliable Sales & Retail Assistant with over 9 years of experience in customer service, sales, and stock management. Strong work ethic and positive attitude, with a track record of helping customers and keeping stores running smoothly. Quick to learn, great at working in teams, and always ready to help. Based in Richmond and ready to join immediately.

mrs.sara.torkamani@gmail.com

L +44 777 132 9796

Richmond, London, UK

Professional Experience

Founder and Manager

Bitty Style Full-time

(1 year 8 months) 07/2020 - 02/2022

- Established an online clothing store and increased sales revenue by 150% by utilizing strategic marketing campaigns, social media engagement, and customer satisfaction programs.
- Created relationships with multiple suppliers, resulting in a diverse product line and 25% higher profit
- Analyzed customer buying patterns and optimized product offerings resulting in a 20% increase in sales revenue within the first quarter of management.

Office Manager

Ermile Full-time

(4 years 7 months) 06/2015 - 12/2019

- Enhanced employee productivity and reduced overhead costs by 30% through implementated and maintenanced of effective office management systems, by reducing paper use, the organization also achieved a more eco-friendly workplace.
- Improved office productivity by renegotiating vendor contracts and finding cost-effective solutions and managed the office relocation project, ensuring a seamless transition and minimizing disruptions.

Sales Associate

Noshahr.com Full-time

(2 years 3 months) 02/2013 - 04/2015

 Achieved over 40% revenue growth by exceeding sales targets through effective communication and building strong customer relationship.

Education

B.S. in English Translation

TMQU - Toloue Mehr Qom Higher Education Institute

2016 - 2021

B.S. in Food Science and Technology

Khazar Institute of Higher Education

2012 - 2014

A.S. in Chemical Industry

TVU - Technical and Vocational University

2010 - 2012

Skills

Collaboration

Presentation

Word

Excel

PowerPoint

Teamwork

Languages

English Fluent B2

Persian Native

Azerbaijani Native